Finding Aid for the Livingston Gearhart Collection of Scores, 1930-1996
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Manuscript score additions, circa 1940-2004, V; Folder 508-663
  - Additional compositions, circa 1940-1976, V.A; Folder 508-519
    - Gearhart, Livingston Perpetual Dorian 1976, 1 score (7 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For 2 violins, 2 violas, and cello (or bass). (Box 27, Folder 515)
    - Gearhart, Livingston Peter and wolf tag undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. Presumably an addition to Prokofiev's Peter and the wolf. (Box 27, Folder 516)
    - Gearhart, Livingston Suite Virginia circa 1954, 1 score (10 pages); Holograph (Ink) For solo piano. For Virginia (Gearhart) Waring. (Box 27, Folder 517)
    - Gearhart, Livingston Untitled piano piece undated, 1 score (3 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For solo piano. (Box 27, Folder 518)
    - Gearhart, Lillian Hawley, 1889-1975 Untitled piano duet undated, 1 score (9 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For 2 pianos. Accompanied by handwritten note by Lillian Gearhart that refers to Respighi piano duets played around Christmas. (Box 27, Folder 519)
  - Additional arrangements, circa 1940-2004, V.B; Folder 520-663
    Arranged into four subseries:
    1. Arrangements for two pianos and orchestra
    2. Arrangements for string trio
    3. Arrangements for instrumental and vocal ensembles
    4. Pedagogical works
    Works arranged by Livingston Gearhart for a variety of musical purposes.
    - Arrangements for two pianos and orchestra, 1940-1950, V.B.1; Folder 520-534
      Arrangements made for use by the Gearhart and Morley piano duo.
      Arranged alphabetically by composer surname and then alphabetically by preferred (uniform) title.
      - Chopin, Frederic, 1810-1849 Rondos, pianos (2), op. 73, C major; arranged Rondo for two pianos between 1940-1950, 1 score (94 pages) and 21 parts; Combination of manuscript and print For 2 pianos and orchestra. Originally for 2 pianos. Arranged by Livingston Gearhart. The score consists of the original printed piano parts glued onto a pencil holograph of the orchestral arrangement. Parts consist of vellum masters plus ozalid reproductions. (Box 28, Folder 520-522)
      - Infante, Manuel, 1883-1958 Danses andalouses. Gracia; arranged Vito between 1940-1950, 1 score (24 pages) and 25 parts; Combination of manuscript and print For 2 pianos and orchestra. Originally for 2 pianos. Arranged by Livingston Gearhart. The score consists of the original printed piano parts glued onto a pencil holograph of the orchestral arrangement. Parts are ozalid reproductions. (Box 28, Folder 523-524)
      - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Rhapsodies hongroises. No 2; arranged Rhapsodie hongroise no. 2 between 1940-1950, 1 score (15 pages) and 31 parts; Combination of manuscript and print For 2 pianos and orchestra. Originally for solo piano. Arranged by Livingston Gearhart. The score consists of the original printed piano part glued onto a pencil holograph of the orchestral arrangement. Parts consist of vellum masters, ozalid reproductions, and manuscripts. (Box 28, Folder 525-526)
      - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943 Preludes, piano, op. 23. No. 5; arranged Prelude op. 23 no. 5 between 1940-1950, 1 score (21 pages) and 29 parts; Combination of manuscript and print For 2 pianos and orchestra. Originally for solo piano. Arranged by Livingston Gearhart. The score consists of the original printed piano part glued onto a pencil holograph of the orchestral arrangement. Parts consist of vellum masters, ozalid reproductions, and manuscripts. (Box 28, Folder 527-528)
      - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943 Suites, pianos (2), no. 1, op. 5. Larmes; arranged Tears between 1940-1950, 1 score (19 pages) and 31 parts; Combination of manuscript and print For 2 pianos and orchestra. Originally for 2 pianos. Arranged by Livingston Gearhart. The score consists of the original printed piano parts glued onto a pencil holograph of the orchestral arrangement. Parts consist of vellum masters, ozalid reproductions, and manuscripts. (Box 29, Folder 529-530)
      - Schulz-Evler, Andrei, 1852-1905 Arabesken über Themen des Walzers An der schönen blauen Donau; arranged Blue Danube waltzes between 1940-1950, 1 score (32 pages) and 27 parts; Combination of manuscript and print For 2 pianos and orchestra. The Schulz-Evler work was originally for solo piano. Gearhart used a two-piano arrangement as the basis for this arrangement. Original music by Johann Strauss (1825-1899). Arranged by Livingston Gearhart. The score consists of the original printed piano parts glued onto a pencil holograph of the orchestral arrangement. Parts consist of vellum masters, ozalid reproductions, and manuscripts. (Box 29, Folder 531-532)
      - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949 Rosenkavalier (Opera). Selections; arranged Rosenkavalier waltzes between 1940-1950, 1 score (19 pages) and 21 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For 2 pianos and orchestra. Arranged by Livingston Gearhart. Parts consist of ozalid reproductions and manuscripts. (Box 29, Folder 533-534)
    - Arrangements for string trio, circa 1960-1980, V.B.2; Folder 535-562
      Arrangements chiefly made for use by Gearhart's son, violinist Fritz Gearhart. All but the last three works in the series were received in a folder marked by Fritz Gearhart: These are all string trio arrangements written for Fritz Gearhart, his son.
      All but the final three works in the series arranged in order that matches the order of works in the compilation created by Fritz Gearhart: String trio gig collection, Vol. 3 available online at http://fritzgearhartmusic.com/String_Trio_Gig_Collection_3.html.
      - Minuet, harpsichord, G major; arranged Minuet in G undated, 1 score (4 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. Formerly attributed to Johann Sebastian Bach. No. 1 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. At head of title: Antiques refinished (the series). (Box 29, Folder 535)
      - Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849 Preludes, piano, op. 28. No. 4; arranged Prelude #4 undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 2 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 536)
      - Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937 Ma mère l'oye (Piano duet). Pavane de la belle au bois dormant; arranged Pavane undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 3 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 537)
      - Paganini, Nicolò, 1782-1840 Caprices, violin, M.S. 25. No. 24; arranged Caprice #24 undated, 1 score (9 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 4 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 538)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Suites, cello, BWV 1008, D minor. Sarabande; arranged Sarabande from Suite in D minor undated, 2 scores; Combination of manuscript and print For violin, viola, and cello. One score consists of the printed solo cello part attached as the viola line to a pencil holograph containing the added violin and cello parts. The other score is a pencil holograph. No. 5 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 539)
      - MacDowell, Edward, 1860-1908 Woodland sketches. To a wild rose; arranged To a wild orchid undated, 1 score (4 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 6 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 540)
      - Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827 Minuets, orchestra, WoO 10. No. 2; arranged Celebrated minuet undated, 1 score (3 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 7 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 541)
      - Garner, Erroll Misty; arranged Misty undated, 1 score (4 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 8 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 542)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Suites, cello, BWV 1009, C major. Bourrée, no. 1; arranged Bourree from Suite in C major undated, 1 score (2 pages); Combination of manuscript and print For violin, viola, and cello. No. 9 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 543)
      - Iste confessor; arranged Iste confessor, based on 13c. Motet undated, 1 score (3 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 10 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 544)
      - Gearhart, Livingston Bachianas Buffalonis undated, 1 score (3 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 11 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 545)
      - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971 Pastorale, soprano, piano; arranged Pastorale undated, 1 score (3 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 12 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 546)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Fugues, organ, BWV 578, G minor; arranged Fugue in G minor undated, 1 score (12 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 13 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 547)
      - Ėĭ ukhnem Volga boatman undated, 1 score (6 pages) and 3 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. Score is pencil holograph and parts are ink manuscript. No. 14 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 548)
      - Hill, Mildred J., 1859-1916 Happy birthday to you; arranged HB undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 15 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 549)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Sonaten und Partiten, violin, BWV 1001-1006. Partita, no. 3. Preludio; arranged Preludio undated, 1 score (12 pages) and 3 parts; Combination of manuscript and print For violin, viola, and cello. The score consists of the printed violin part attached to a pencil holograph of the accompanying viola and cello parts. There are separate manuscript parts for viola and cello, and a pencil manuscript part with both viola and cello. No. 16 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 550)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Suites, cello, BWV 1007, G major. Prélude; arranged Prelude from G major suite #1 undated, 1 score (6 pages); Combination of manuscript and print For violin, viola, and cello. Score consists of printed cello part attached to pencil holograph of accompanying violin and viola parts. No. 17 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 551)
      - Gearhart, Livingston Variations on a British air undated, 2 scores (10 and 11 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. Based on London Bridge is falling down. Pencil holograph score is lacking final page. Photocopy of pencil holograph includes final page. No. 18 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 552)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Inventions, harpsichord, BWV 795, F minor; arranged Sinfonia IX (version in A minor): abbreviated from the orig. J.S. Bach undated, 4 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. Parts for violin, viola, cello B (middle voice), and cello C (bottom part). Accompanied by typescript performance notes. No. 21 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 553)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Orgelbüchlein. Ich ruf' zu dir, Herr Jesu Christ; arranged Ich ruf zu dir undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 22 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 554)
      - Denza, Luigi Funiculì funiculà; arranged Funiculì funiculà undated, 1 score (3 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. Lacking title. No. 23 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 555)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Praeludium undated, 1 score (3 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. Unable to identify the original work. No. 24 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 556)
      - Cottrau, Teodoro, 1827-1879 Santa Lucia; arranged Santa Lucia undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 25 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 557)
      - De Curtis, Ernesto, 1875-1937 Torna a Surriento; arranged Come back to Sorrento undated, 1 score (3 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. No. 26 in String trio gig collection, Vol. 3. (Box 29, Folder 558)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Wohltemperierte Klavier, 1. T. Nr. 3. Fuga; arranged Fugue in G major undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. Incomplete work. Lacking title. (Box 29, Folder 559)
      - Gearhart, Livingston In a Persian garden undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. Incomplete work. At head of title: Antiques refinished. (Box 29, Folder 560)
      - Gearhart, Livingston Petit rien undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Photocopy) For violin, viola, and cello. Accompanied by manuscript note: Trio written for students on different levels - easy Vla part. (Box 29, Folder 561)
      - Serradell, Narcisco, 1843-1910 Golondrina; arranged Golondrina (The swallow) undated, 1 score (4 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. (Box 29, Folder 562)
    - Arrangements for instrumental and vocal ensembles, circa 1960-1990, V.B.3; Folder 559-612
      Arrangements chiefly for larger instrumental ensembles.
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 2. Allegro assai; arranged Brandenburg undated, 1 score (24 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin and full orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 563)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Orgelbüchlein. Alte Jahr vergangen ist Old year is gone undated, 1 score (2 pages) and 1 part; Holograph (Pencil) Possibly for violin, flute, or oboe with string orchestra accompaniment. Might also be for string quartet. Part is ink manuscript for solo part. (Box 30, Folder 564)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Orgelbüchlein. Christ lag in Todesbanden, BWV 625; arranged Christ lag in Todesbanden (Good Friday chorale); Liebster Jesu, Wir sind hier (Chorale prelude) undated, 1 score (4 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For string orchestra. Liebster Jesu, Wir sind hier is BWV 633. (Box 30, Folder 565)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Prelude, G major; arranged WTC prelude undated, 1 score (4 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For violin, viola, and cello. The original work has not been identified but has not been found in either book of Bach's Well-Tempered Clavier. (Box 30, Folder 566)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Sonaten und Partiten, violin, BWV 1001-1006. Partita, no. 3. Preludio; arranged Theme music (under solo) undated, 1 score (1 page) and 3 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For solo violin with violin, viola, and cello accompaniment. Arrangement of the opening of the Preludio from Bach's Partita for solo violin in E major, BWV 1006. Incomplete (Box 30, Folder 567)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Verschiedene Vorspiele über die Catechismus- und andere Gesaenge. Kyrie, Gott heiliger Geist, BWV 671; arranged Ricercare: Kyrie Gott, heiliger Geise undated, 1 score (20 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 568)
      - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Verschiedene Vorspiele über die Catechismus- und andere Gesaenge. Wir glauben all an einen Gott, BWV 680; arranged Chorale prelude in D minor: Wir glauben all' an einen Gott, Schopfer November 1961, 1 score (14 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. This arrangement is possibly not by Gearhart, but by T. Sullivan. Compare to Gearhart's arrangement of the same work in Folder 135 in the collection. On title page Work number XII for organ from the Pianoforte Practice part III (number 60 in the C.F. Peters February, 1928 edition) transcribed for small orchestra by T. Sullivan. (Box 30, Folder 569)
      - Barnby, Joseph, 1838-1896 O perfect love; arranged O perfect love undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For string quartet. (Box 30, Folder 570)
      - Barnby, Joseph, Sir, 1838-1896 Sweet and low; arranged Sweet and low undated, 1 score (1 page); Holograph (Pencil) For three unspecified bass clef instruments. In caption: Bass clef sessions pg. 54. (Box 30, Folder 571)
      - Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827 Allegro und Menuetto, flutes (2), WoO 26, G major. Menuetto; arranged Minuet: Allegro moderato undated, 1 score (3 pages); Combination of manuscript and print For two unspecified treble clef instruments with string orchestra accompaniment. Originally for two flutes. Accompanied by typescript note indicating this is Version III of this arrangement. (Box 30, Folder 572)
      - Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827 Allegro und Menuetto, flutes (2), WoO 26, G major. Menuetto; arranged Minuet: Version II undated, 1 score (4 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For two unspecified treble clef instruments with string orchestra accompaniment. Originally for two flutes. Only the uppermost part is indicated on the score. (Box 30, Folder 573)
      - Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990 West Side story. Tonight; arranged Ce soir undated, 1 score (8 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 574)
      - Borodin, Aleksandr Porfirʹevich, 1833-1887 Kni︠a︡zʹ Igorʹ. Pli︠a︡ska polovet︠s︡kikh devushek; arranged Danse: from Prince Igor, #8 undated, 1 score (30 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 575)
      - Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897 Lieder, op. 86. Feldeinsamkeit; arranged Summer reverie; Cotton needs pickin undated, 3 scores; Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. Two scores (3 pages each) of the Brahms arrangement: 1 in G major, 1 in B-flat major. One score (5 pages) for arrangement of traditional work song, Cotton needs pickin. The two works were received within the same wrapper with a single work number: G 37. Note on the outer wrapper: L.G. - Chorus and orch. (Box 30, Folder 576)
      - Caldara, Antonio, 1670-1736 Come raggio di sol; arranged Come raggio di sol undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For string orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 577)
      - Chausson, Ernest, 1855-1899 Poème, violin, orchestra; arranged Poème undated, 2 scores; Combination of manuscript and print For violin and piano. Both scores are photocopies and consist of a printed score with manuscript interpolations. One score is spiral bound; the loose score includes portions taped onto the score. Both Accompanied by manuscript notes about the score from Fritz Gearhart to Pamela Gearhart. (Box 30, Folder 578)
      - Clarke, Jeremiah, 1669?-1707 Trumpet voluntary, harpsichord; arranged Trumpet voluntary undated, 1 score (9 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. As was customary at the time, the work is attributed to Purcell on the title page. (Box 30, Folder 579)
      - Eccles, Henry, active 1694-1735 Sonatas, violin, continuo, book 1. No. 11. Largo; arranged Eccles (I) undated, 1 score 3 pages) and 4 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For double bass solo and string orchestra. Parts for violin A and B, Viola, and Cello D. (Box 30, Folder 580)
      - Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946 Cancion del fuego fatuo: Song of the will o the wisp undated, 1 score (7 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For unspecified treble solo, oboe, and string orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 581)
      - Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924 Après un rêve; arranged Apres un reve undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For unspecified treble solo and string orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 582)
      - Gershwin, George, 1898-1937 Lady be good! Man I love; arranged Man I love undated, 1 score (2 pages) and 5 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For string orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 583)
      - God rest ye, merry gentlemen; arranged God rest ye merry, gentlemen 1975, 1 score (4 pages) and 4 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For string quartet. (Box 30, Folder 584)
      - Gold, Ernest, 1921-1999 Exodus. Main theme; arranged Theme from X undated, 1 score (10 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 585)
      - Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963 Mathis der Maler (Symphony). Grablegung; arranged Grablegung (Entombment) (Mathis der Maler II) 1973, 1 score (8 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 586)
      - Holst, Gustav, 1874-1934 Double concerto. Variations on a ground; arranged Variations over a ground undated, 1 score (20 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. Contains differences from photocopy of this score in Folder 169. (Box 30, Folder 587)
      - Hosianna; arranged Hosianna (Swedish hymn) undated, 1 score (8 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For string orchestra. (Box 30, Folder 588)
      - Hovhaness, Alan, 1911-2000 Etchmiadzin (Opera). Prayer of Saint Gregory; arranged Prayer of St. Gregory undated, 1 part (4 pages); Computer notated For 2 trumpets and band. No location stated: International Trumpet Guild, 2011 This is an arrangement for 2 trumpets and band. The part is for both trumpets. It is meant to be used with the score published by Peer International. The part for 2 trumpets was made available online via the International Trumpet Guild October 2011. Accompanied by 2 pages of photocopy of holograph of final two pages of Gearhart's part for two trumpets. Also accompanied by correspondence between Kim Dunnick and Pamela Gearhart, and Pamela and Fritz Gearhart about the arrangement. (Box 31, Folder 589)
      - Kreisler, Fritz, 1875-1962 Präludium und Allegro, violin, piano; arranged Praeludium undated, 1 score (20 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For solo violin and orchestra. Solo line chiefly left blank, assuming it was available via the printed score. Accompanied by typescript explanatory note. (Box 31, Folder 590)
      - Kreisler, Fritz, 1875-1962 Tambourine chinois; arranged Tambourine chinoise undated, 1 score (8 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For solo violin and string orchestra. (Box 31, Folder 591)
      - Lloyd Webber, Andrew, 1948- Cats. Memory; arranged Memory undated, 1 score (4 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For string quartet. (Box 31, Folder 592)
      - Marcello, Benedetto, 1686-1739 Quella fiamma che m'accende; arranged My joyful ardor: recitative and aria undated, 2 scores; Print (Photocopy) For voice and keyboard. Attached to the verso of both scores are a violin and viola part (photocopy of manuscript) for an unspecified work. First line of text: Il mio bel foco. Possibly attributed now to Francesco Bartolomeo Conti. (Box 31, Folder 593)
      - Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912 Elegies, medium voice, cello, piano; arranged Elegie undated, 1 score (5 pages) and 4 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For solo double bass, tuba, contrabassoon, ophicleide, or serpent and string orchestra. On title page: 1st version, later revised. (Box 31, Folder 594)
      - Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912 Elegies, medium voice, cello, piano; arranged Elegie: Version II undated, 1 score (7 pages) and 5 parts; Holograph (Pencil) For solo double bass and string orchestra. Includes inserted accompaniment for cadenza. (Box 31, Folder 595)
      - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847 Sommernachtstraum. Notturno Nocturne from Midsummer night's dream undated, 1 score (20 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. (Box 31, Folder 596)
      - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 Kleine Nachtmusik; arranged Eine kleine brouhaha undated, 1 score (4 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For string orchestra. (Box 31, Folder 597)
      - Paganini, Nicolò, 1782-1840 Concertos, violin, orchestra, no. 2, op. 7, B minor. Rondo; arranged Campanella undated, 1 score (11 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For solo violin and orchestra. (Box 31, Folder 598)
      - Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953 Pieces, piano, op. 12. Marsh; arranged Marche, op. 12, no. 1 undated, 1 score (12 pages); Holograph (Pencil) For orchestra. Includes score of original version for solo piano and a short score/sketch of the arrangement. (Box 31, Folder 599)